you're gonna admit it we're all just a
little bit dumb you know like men don't
even try to argue with women that's
never gonna happen we're too dumb to
argue with women women are too smart
we're just dumb like a man arguing with
a woman is like going to battle a chess
grandmaster and we brought Connect four
to the game you know I'm saying like
wait we're already a checkmate right
like weasels argument where's your ring
like every single day you wake up like
gonna get in trouble just don't know
when it's gonna happen
[Music]
like one time I walked out in the
kitchen if my lady was like yup knew and
what did you know how did I screw that
up I walked in I walked out am i walking
weird she's like I knew it I knew you
weren't going to unload the dishwasher
are there even dishes in it I don't know
but you don't either because you didn't
bother to check I win daggett are you so
good at this the one that may be the
craziest this happens to every man in
here this happen to every single guy at
some one time your life you walk into a
grocery store with a woman they just
throw their purse in the car and walk
off and now that's your purse you got to
watch that purse
how rude and presumptuous as if I don't
have important things to do right now
right I gotta watch the first one if I
want to walk around get stuff done I
don't know if I'm gonna walk around and
just go look at the fruit snacks and the
Bagel Bites and other things they used
to buy when I was really happy you know
[Applause]
just walk down the cereal aisle and
touch every single box that I may just
touch em all it's all fruity pebbles we
had a good run didn't we just walk into
the freezer Pizza section open the door
just waft the cold air me bask in the
cold air from the stuffed-crust
DiGiorno's it feels so good yeah
important things it drove me crazy maybe
crazy cuz he kept checking up on me
to see if I was watching the purse made
me crazy are you watching effort yeah
yeah yeah yeah right there see it I'm
four feet away I see your purse now are
you watching what yeah yeah you know I'm
watching it you know at this point I
dare someone take a shot at this purse
because you made me take one overpriced
kickboxing class and then kinda see if
it works that's what I want to see if my
90 bucks is worth the skills I'm baiting
people in like 6 feet away I might ride
I dare you somebody take a shot of that
person I can hear her voice he's driving
me crazy on the other aisle over it's
like baby yeah somewhat yes yeah
watching yeah look over her purse is now
gone her purse god I start panicking I'm
getting neck sweat I'm having an anxiety
attack I'm gonna think about how my plan
my own death she doesn't win this
argument right she comes walking around
the corner of the aisle holding her
purse above her head she's you are not
watching my purse I stole my own purse
what you can't steal your own purse
that's an inside job what are you doing
can't walk right up to the card and I
took my own personal yeah because you
have security clearance we talked about
I had a perimeter set up and you had
access kinda made me crazy cuz that's a
long ways to go to win an argument right
there setup you know I mean that's a lot
and she wanted to have kids at the time
that would have gone poorly what if I'm
watching the kids at the park
are you watching yes I'm watching the
kids yeah yeah yeah you watch yes it's
like you open steamapps you are not
watching our kids I abducted our own
kids they are tied up in a van with duct
tape over their mouths I won this
argument
you